mundanefaithfulness.com 2013-05-27

# Privacy Policy | Westside Church

Westside Church is committed to maintaining your trust and confidence. The following online privacy policy is to protect and secure the personal information you provide to our ministry online.

### Copyright

All content on this website is Copyright 2013 Westside Church.

### Awareness

Westside Church provides this online policy to make sure you are aware of our security practices and to inform you of the way your information is collected and used. We also provide you with the opportunity to remove your name from our mailing list, if you desire to do so.

### Information we collect

There are two different ways in which we collect information from visitors on our Web site:

1\. From persons interested in requesting information or materials from our organization; and  
2\. From our online donations.

The online information that we collect includes name, address, city, state, zip, telephone number, e-mail address, and, in the case of online giving, credit card number and expiration date. In order to continuously improve your service and tailor our subsequent communications to you, we may also ask you to provide us with enough information regarding your demographics, comments, professional interests, and contact preferences.

### How is the information used

Westside Church uses your information to understand your needs and provide you with better service. We may use your information to complete a transaction, issue you an income tax receipt for a donation, or to personalize our Web site for you. If you so desire, we may also use this information to update you on ministry projects and activities. Credit card numbers are used only for donation or payment processing and are not retained for any other purposes. We also provide you the opportunity to remove your name from our mailing list, if you desire to do so. Please review the corresponding section of this privacy policy below.

### No sharing of personal information

Westside Church never sells, rents, leases, or exchanges your personal information with other organizations. Westside Church assures you that the identity of all who contact us through this Web site will be kept confidential. Use of personal information will be limited to the internal purposes of Westside Church and only to further the ministry activities and purposes of Westside Church.

### Security

Westside Church is committed to ensuring the security of your personal information. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the proper use of information, we have established and implemented appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. Westside Church uses Internet Encryption Software, Secure Socket Layer (SSL) Protocol when collecting or transferring sensitive data such as credit card information. Any information you enter is encrypted at your browser, sent over the public Internet in encrypted form, then de-encrypted at our server. Once we receive your credit card information, it is accessible only to a small number of trusted Westside Church staff who have been specially trained in processing this information.

### Removing your name from our mailing list

Our Web site gives you the opportunity to remove your name from our mailing list so that you do not receive any future communications from our ministry. If you desire to remove your name, you can send us an e-mail at:  **info “at” westsidechurchpca.org**

If you determine that information in our database is inaccurate or it has changed, you may modify the previously provided information by sending an e-mail to:  **info “at” westsidechurchpca.org**

### Contacting Us

If you have comments or questions about our privacy policy, please send us an e-mail at:  **info “at” westsidechurchpca.org**
